2, 1, 0 ... All engines running.
Liftoff. We have a liftoff 32 minutes past the hour. Liftoff on Apollo 11.
40 feet, down 2 1/2. Kicking up some dust. 30 feet, 2 1/2 down. Faint shadow. 4 forward.
4 forward. Drifting to the right a little. Okay. Down a half.
Contact light. OK, engine stop.
Houston, Tranquility Base here. The Eagle has landed.
Roger, Tranquility. We copy you on the ground. You got a bunch of guys about to turn blue.
We're breathing again. Thanks a lot.
Ok, Neil, we can see you coming down the ladder now.
I'm at the foot of the ladder. The LM footpads are only
depressed in the surface about 1 or 2 inches.
I'm going to step off the LM now.
That's one small step for a man, one giant leap for mankind.
Yahoo! Tony, this is so great you can't believe it!
Oh, I believe it, Charlie.
It's running, John!
Look at it go, would you, Charlie!
You've got all your steering. It's great!
Ah, this is going to be some kind of different ride!
Hippity-hoppity, hippity-hoppity, hippity-hopping over hill and dale.
Da da da da da da da da da da da da da.
Hippity-hopping all along.
One ignition.
We're on our way, Houston.
Things are good. Looks good. Gotcha.
Standby for flag down.
Recovery. A landing. Standby.